Nikola Stanchev



Contact

Address:

Strelbishte 112, Sofia, Bulgaria

Phone:

+359 876626284

Email:

nikolastanchev4@gmail.com

Languages

English - C1

Summary

I'm a Computer Engineering student with rich experience in robotics. A fast learning, adaptive and motivated person, with great teamworking skills, accumulated whilst representing Bulgaria in multiple world robotics competitions.

Skill Highlights

- Problem solving
- Quickly adaptive
- Fast learning
- Innovative
- Teamwork skills

Experience

Robotics team mentor - 3/2020 to 9/2020 **Robopartans**, Bulgaria

- Coordination with organizing party
- Creation of short-term schedule
- Management of team members
- Organization of team building exercises

Robot Designer/Builder - 10/2017 to 03/2018 **Robopartans**, Bulgaria

- Design of robots for specific needs
- Building of robots
- Building 3D models with instructions

Full-Stack Web Developer Internship – 12/2021 to present

- Front-end development with HTML, CSS
- Back-end development with PHP

Education

Sofia University St. Kliment Ohridski

Bachelor of Computer Engineering | 2020 – present

22 SOU Georgi S. Rakovski

Graduated class of 2020

Certifications

English: IELTS

Clean driving license